# Marko Andrushchenko



refineanswer@gmail.com



https://join.skype.com/invite/aRoWHBwvtQ



linkedin.com/in/stardusted1



https://t.me/Std\_1

## **Summary**

Hello, I'm experienced and reliable Flutter (Android) developer.

Currently engaged in the development using such technologies as:

- Mobile: Flutter(Dart/Firebase);

I have experience in developing using such technologies as:

- Java Spring (Hibernate/PostgreSQL);
- React.js (JavaScript/CSS/JQuery 3.6/Bootstrap 4) Webpack|Gulp / SCSS;
- AngularJS (v.1.x)
- Django (Python);

## **Experience**



### **Mobile Application Developer**

NDA

Jun 2020 - Nov 2020 (6 months)

Worked on some stuff with cloud firestore, firebase messaging

## -

## Mobile Application Developer

Freelance, self-employed

Apr 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

Reminder - a project to help managers track completing tasks.

PHP, pure JS, Flutter(Dart)

Have worked as a mobile developer.

## -

#### Fullstack Developer

Freelance, self-employed

Feb 2019 - Jun 2019 (5 months)

Readland - bookstore.

Django, pure JS, Postgres, Bootstrap 4.

SCRUM management.

Have worked as a fullstack developer.

### Frontend Web Developer

Freelance, self-employed

Dec 2018 - May 2019 (6 months)

Medicus - a project to help doctors interact with patients.

PHP, Firebase, pure JS, Bootstrap 4.

Scrum management.

Worked as a designer and frontend developer.

Started as a junior and finished as a middle frontend developer.

### **Education**

## Markiv National University of Radioelectronics

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2017 - 2021

### **Licenses & Certifications**

Multithreading in iOS(Swift) - Stepic

https://stepik.org/cert/245877

JavaScript Course Certificate - SoloLearn

Java Course Certificate - SoloLearn

### **Skills**

Flutter • Dart • Android SDK • Java • React.js